♪ As flowers bloom and wither ♪
♪ May we pass by the magnificent scenery ♪
♪ Contemplate the vastness
of Heaven and Earth ♪
♪ Could it be that both of us
are filled with desolation? ♪
♪ As flowers bloom and wither ♪
♪ May we lead such a life ♪
♪ Contemplate the vastness
of Heaven and Earth ♪
♪ Turning back, you and I ♪
♪ Seize the current moment ♪
♪ The sky is painted
with a gentle pallet of pastel colors ♪
♪ Let's walk together ♪
♪ Even if ♪
♪ The snow in front of us ♪
♪ Will dye our hair white ♪
♪ In an instant ♪
[Joy of Life Season 2]
[Adapted from Mao Ni's Joy of Life
on Yuewen Group's Qidian platform]
[Episode 16]
The one sitting inside,
you better show yourself!
Mr. Fan,
these youngsters have
quite the background.
Their fathers are either
dukes or marquises.
Sons of those nobles and generals?
I suppose they are just nobles.
Some must be from the military family.
Right.
But we can't fight them
in public.
I have taken note...
He is scared.
of their faces.
Why don't we teach them some lessons
in private afterward?
As long as we don't show our faces,
we can beat them up
however we want.
That sounds right.
But today,
I feel like showing my face.
So you are Fan Xian?
I heard that you brat took over
the Baoyue Pleasure House.
Cut your crap.
Do you know whose property
the Baoyue Pleasure House is?
You are in no place
to take over His Highness' property.
Be sensible and return it.
I will spare your life.
I see, it's the Third Prince.
Let me guess.
He doesn't know about this, right?
You want to claim
the Baoyue Pleasure House
to impress His Highness.
What's with that huff?
Do you know
you are causing him trouble?
Your threats are empty.
Just hand over the property.
Believe it or not,
if you don't,
I'm going to take your life right here.
I doubt it.
You don't think I dare kill you here?
Get him!
I'm falling!
Two injured.
Three
injured.
These brats actually
have the nerve to mess with Fan Xian.
They have been well-protected
since little,
yet they are still so naive
at this age.
If so, we should get prepared
to take this advantage against Fan Xian.
He always wants to seek justice,
doesn't he?
Let's grant him his wish.
Go to Ye's Residence to see Ye Ling'er.
Tell her that I'm grounded,
I can't go out.
I would like to invite her over.
I don't think she would come.
Tell her it's about the conflict
between me and Fan Xian.
She will come.
Miss Ye and Princess Lin are tight.
She also gets along well with Fan Xian.
She might not take your side
to confront Fan Xian.
I need someone
to bring me a ladder.
Move!
Clear the way!
How dare you!
Mr. Fan,
I'm late.
Move aside!
Do you recognize these people?
I do.
Their parents
are the court...
Are you sure?
I made
a mistake?
I don't know them at all.
These unknown brats
tried to stop the inspector's carriage
in the middle of the road.
Should I
arrest them?
You decide.
Take them away!
Yes!
Get up!
How dare you arrest me!
Aren't you afraid
of your whole family being executed?
- Stay still.
- Gentlemen,
do them a favor and shut up.
Mr. Fan, do I really arrest them?
Of course.
And then?
Then,
search them for silver taels
to compensate the affected shop owners.
These brats used too much strength.
Isn't Mr. Fan
wise and compassionate?
Off you go.
I suppose the Second Prince plotted this
to divide you and the Third Prince.
I know.
Let's not fall into his trap.
Go to the First Division.
All right.
Surrender all your money.
Wang Qinian.
Yes, Mr. Fan.
Change the route to the palace.
Wait, Mr. Fan.
We can't fall into his trap.
I'm angry and just can't get over this.
What is he doing up there?
No idea.
Is this the way he entertains his guests?
No.
Should I go up there too?
You don't have to.
His Highness said it's your choice.
Thank you for coming here.
I prepared all this for you.
Help yourself.
Why are you sitting here?
Would you believe me
if I said it was a misunderstanding
between Fan Xian and me?
But look what you two have become.
Still, I admire him deep inside.
You should tell him.
Why did you invite me here instead?
He might not come.
Our misunderstanding has run too deep.
Honestly,
I have never played dirty tricks
against him.
If you don't believe me,
look into my eyes.
I swear on the dignity
of the imperial family.
May I ask,
why are you telling me all this?
I was forced to.
Can you tell me
who can force a prince?
His Majesty.
I want to stay out of conflicts.
He won't let me.
He praised me
in front of those officials,
made me a lord at 13,
and let me attend the court session
at 15.
He wouldn't allow me
to leave the Capital.
He offered me chances
to form alliances with the officials.
How will the Crown Prince think of me?
If I said I never meant to compete,
would he believe me?
Hence, I can only obey and move forward.
If I were
to turn back now,
I would die a pathetic death.
Why did His Majesty do so?
He makes me a pacemaker
for the Crown Prince.
That's a treasonous thing to say.
That's why I say it on the roof.
No one hears me.
If you are afraid of that,
why are you telling me?
We are engaged.
Since we can't defy this marriage,
we have a shared destiny
for the rest of our lives.
If I must
find someone in this world
to open my heart to,
it should be you.
By now, you should believe
that I mean no harm
to Fan Xian.
Hold on.
I'm confused.
You confessed to your fiancee
to prove that it was a misunderstanding
between you and Fan Xian.
It doesn't feel right, though.
I'm grounded now.
Except for you,
no one will see me.
So?
So I would like you
to deliver a memorandum to the palace.
What memorandum?
A recommendation letter.
Who are you recommending?
Fan Xian.
Keep talking.
According to the latest news
from the Imperial Inspectorate,
there were peers interrupting
Fan Xian's carriage on the street.
Fan Xian injured three of them.
Now, they are all detained
in the First Division.
That's trivial, though.
Why did you have to report this
personally?
I wanted to avoid noise.
You may now know about this.
All those dukes are crowding
at the Imperial Inspectorate's entrance.
They want me to release their sons.
That's why you hid here?
There is no other quiet place
than here, Your Majesty.
Why did you back off?
Your Majesty,
is this the gunpowder?
Yes.
Tell me.
Does the First Division
not want to release them?
Your Majesty, it was Fan Xian
who arrested them.
I will have to ask Fan Xian
before releasing them.
Go look for him, then.
Fan Xian...
He is also hiding in the palace.
Kneel.
Do you own the Baoyue Pleasure House?
Fan Sizhe is the first owner.
So you got a share in this.
Fan Sizhe said
it was a lucrative business.
If Fan Sizhe tells you to eat poop,
will you eat that too?
Fan Sizhe wouldn't do that.
Why are you defending him?
He didn't.
How dare you egg on those young masters
to block Fan Xian's carriage!
I didn't.
Let me ask you one more time.
Are you behind this?
No.
Fine, you are still denying it.
Maids.
Bring me the rattan cane!
Mother, I didn't instruct them
to stop the carriage.
Aunt Liu, please calm down.
His Highness wouldn't do
such silly things.
What's wrong with you people?
Why are you still fishing here
when Aunt Liu is so angry?
Bring her the cane right now.
[Concubine Yi, mother of Third Prince]
You better own up!
- Mother!
- Own up already!
It hurts.
No?
Own up!
Mother.
Own up now!
Mother, please stop.
Brat!
Aunt Liu, please calm down.
You are going nowhere!
Nowhere!
Don't you run!
Don't run!
I'm going to beat you to death!
Aunt Liu, take a break.
Brat!
You are so disappointing!
Aunt Liu, please take a sip.
It wasn't me, Mother.
Brat!
Stop beating me.
Give me a minute. Let me beat him first.
There isn't much to do on rainy days.
I might as well
give him a good spanking.
Own up!
Mother, I didn't.
Aunt Liu, do you want to stop
and go fishing?
The maids are here watching this.
I don't care who is here.
Fishing helps me pass the time,
and so does caning him.
Own up!
Stop denying!
I didn't do that!
Brat!
Please stop, Mother!
Is she canning him with a rattan?
Indeed.
Do you think we should go
and take a look?
It's too late.
It's done.
That's fast.
Fan Xian stopped her.
No fun.
I missed the fun.
You tell me.
Why do you always know
the news in the palace
sooner than me?
Because the Imperial Inspectorate
is your discerning eye, Your Majesty.
So Lai Mingcheng was right.
The Imperial Inspectorate
has become too autonomous.
He was right.
I see his point now.
Please reconsider that, Your Majesty.
Reconsider?
You always want me to reconsider.
What's there to reconsider?
Whatever Lai Mingcheng said was wrong.
Because he was flogged to death
by your order.
If he was right...
Such audacity.
I pledge my loyalty to you.
And I speak without hiding things.
Aren't you afraid
of ending up like Lai Mingcheng one day?
I wouldn't fear to sacrifice
for the country.
As if.
If you don't fear,
why did you back off just now?
Your Majesty,
it depends on the way of dying.
Smooth talker.
This brat is so stubborn.
Simmer down.
You may go.
Why did you take the cane away?
I'm not done yet.
Aunt Liu,
I believe he knew nothing
about that incident.
I had no idea at all.
Someone purposely did this
to upset us.
Stay in the palace from now on.
Did you hear me?
Xian,
please look out for him.
We are relatives.
He should call you cousin.
Please don't say that, Aunt Liu.
His Highness is a prince.
Yes, but the prince should
also respect their relatives.
Greet him.
Cousin Xian.
Look, he is cute.
Come.
Are those people from noble families?
Yes, they are sons of the dukes.
Did you arrest all of them?
Yes.
You have offended a lot of people, then.
I'm not afraid.
Silly boy. How can it be?
The officialdom is
all about people skills.
His Majesty made me
an isolated official.
I could only choose to be impartial.
Don't tell anyone what you heard.
I dare not.
Oh, boy.
You can't just speak so recklessly.
I won't say this outside.
You are my family.
It has been tough for you.
Aunt Liu.
Don't let him out
for the next few days.
Someone might still be looking
for a chance.
Don't worry. I will keep an eye on him
and not let him out.
I'm leaving, then.
No rush. Stay for a while more.
After all, you are his cousin.
You are relatives.
Please come here often to visit him
and guide him.
Just beat him if he does anything wrong.
He's all yours.
Is there a problem?
I'm saying,
please come here often, Cousin Xian.
Well, you have already beaten him.
I believe he will remember this lesson.
Get up.
Will you still go
to the Baoyue Pleasure House?
No, not anymore.
I was deceived.
The Baoyue Pleasure House
is yours from now on.
Aunt Liu, I'm leaving.
By the way,
the palace sent some yogurt.
I know this is your favorite.
I will have someone
send it to your residence.
The yogurt is flavorful and tasty.
Thank you, Aunt Liu.
Please stay for the meal.
I can't. Those dukes are waiting.
Xian,
take care.
I will. Thank you, Aunt Liu.
Xian, walk slowly.
Stay in touch with him.
Cousin Xian?
But he is competing with Chengze.
Chengze is grounded now.
Listen carefully.
Whether or not
you are safe in the future
depends on Fan Xian.
The Baoyue Pleasure House incident
is a trap set for you.
The palace is a dangerous place.
To be honest, I don't want you
to stay in the Capital.
Do you understand?
Mother,
I understand.
Did I hurt you just now?
Did it hurt?
No.
No?
Not at all.
How could you remember the lesson, then?
Maids.
Bring me
the rattan cane right now!
Did you all hear me?
Bring me the rattan cane! Now!
Brat, you had better come back here!
I'm telling you,
I will beat you
until you learn the lesson!
Did you hear me?
Come back here!
I'm so furious.
Your Majesty, the Ye family
hands in a memorandum.
Show it to Mr. Chen.
This is against the rules.
It's like you never broke the rules.
Everything you say is right.
[Li Chengze and Ye Zhong,
Grand Commandant of the Capital]
This is a joint memorandum
of the Ye family and the Second Prince.
Your Majesty,
Fan Xian inherits
Zhuang Mohan's collection
and possesses
exceptional literary talents.
They recommend Fan Xian
as the examiner
for the coming spring exam.
What's your read
on this recommendation letter?
The Second Prince is smart.
He just got confined, and now
he has submitted a joint memorandum
with the Ye family,
who is protected
by Grandmaster Ye Liuyun.
This joint memorandum
will guarantee him a bright future.
I appointed his marriage
with the Ye family.
He made a clever move,
but it's because of you.
Is this all you can see?
Besides,
despite the conflict with Fan Xian,
he immediately recommends him
for the post.
I'm moved.
Enough about personnel matters.
What else should we talk about?
I'm thinking
if Fan Xian is able
to host the spring exam
at his age.
What's that face?
Your Majesty.
I...
I can't make any comments.
You said you don't want to talk
about personnel matters.
But Fan Xian is a person.
The spring exam is important.
I wouldn't dare to overstep.
I will obey your decision.
Mr. Chen, you always speak
with perfect discretion.
Because I'm your loyal subject.
I made it!
Mr. Fan.
His Majesty has a decree.
What a coincidence.
I was just about to leave.
What decree does His Majesty have?
According to His Majesty,
as spring exam is around the corner,
Fan Xian is appointed as
the fourth-ranked Middle Examiner
to monitor the spring exam.
Congratulations, Mr. Fan.
The current batch of scholars
should revere you as "sir".
Middle Examiner?
This is an interesting title.
Did His Majesty come up with this title?
No.
It has existed since ancient times.
Sir, do you think
I should take neither side
and stay in the middle?
I wouldn't know about that.
Either side you choose, you will
always take the side of His Majesty.
Thank you for your reminder, Eunuch Hou.
Please don't say that.
This isn't a reminder.
I was just saying.
Well, I don't have
any silver taels with me.
You must be kidding me.
It isn't appropriate.
I wouldn't dare to take it.
I have delivered the decree.
I should head back to serve His Majesty.
[Fan's Residence]
It's moving its head.
No, it's looking at me.
Xian, you are back.
- Greetings, Young Master.
Drop the formalities.
Tell your mother
to prepare a lighter meal tomorrow.
- All right, Young Master.
- Got it, Young Master.
Why did you come here?
Were you afraid
of stitching up its wound?
It's done.
Done?
I have already patched it up.
It looks all right.
You sewn it quite well.
After all, I have read
a lot of medical records.
By the way, Xian,
the chloroform you gave
is quite effective.
It didn't wake up halfway.
Were you not scared?
Not really.
Have you ever thought
if you failed?
I would roast and eat it.
Right.
But I think
you are more suitable as a vet.
No, I wouldn't think of that
when I treat humans.
Ruoruo,
as a physician,
not only do you have to be bold,
but you also have to be meticulous
and have steady hands.
What should I do?
Here, pinch it.
Level the needle and lift it higher.
You hid so many needles in your hair.
It adds volume to my hair.
That makes sense.
Well, enough of that.
Hold it steadily.
Don't let it fall.
What should I do next?
Your hand is quite steady.
Then, you learn
how to maintain the balance while moving.
First, you need to walk around.
At the end of the practice,
no matter how you walk,
where you walk,
or even with a blindfold,
make sure the needle won't drop.
When I practiced this back then,
- my master said...
- What's next?
Is this
your first time?
Yes.
Your hand is steady.
Am I pretty gifted as a physician?
Kind of.
Did you practice this before?
Yes.
Did you hold the needle
and walk around like I do?
More or less.
Ruoruo,
no need to practice anymore.
Listen.
This is just the first step.
It's superficial.
The most insignificant skill
of all.
If you want to be a physician,
you have to read a lot
and memorize the position
of the organs
and acupoints.
Then, get a fruit.
Fruit?
Yes.
Cut it open and stitch it back together.
Repeat this procedure
and practice continuously.
It's to train your dexterity
and your patience.
All right.
Should I practice now?
There is no rush.
That's all for today.
I'm leaving, then.
Xian, I'm so forgetful.
Wan'er asked for you.
You are here.
You figured I would come at night?
Mr. Fan,
you always come here at night.
You are saying
like I'm a bad guy.
I heard about
the incident earlier today.
I suppose Chengze was behind this.
I know.
Those lads are only his pawns.
Speaking of them,
just beat and lecture them
if you have to.
With His Majesty's support,
those dukes and nobles
wouldn't dare to intervene.
If anything were to happen,
I will apologize to them.
After all, I'm the princess.
They could do nothing
but swallowing their anger.
Wan'er,
we are truly a couple of geniuses.
The incident earlier today
may seem dangerous,
but it doesn't affect you much.
If Chengze intended
to take revenge against you,
he wouldn't have used
such an obvious trick.
So you think he used this revenge
as a disguise?
To lower your guard
and mislead you.
But in fact,
the sinister plan will ensue.
The spring exam is the real deal.
I remember the last person
who mentioned this
was also him.
If Chengze is going
to lay a trap against you,
the spring exam is the best stage.
The spring exam
holds great importance
for all scholars nationwide.
They study tirelessly
for days and nights
and endures all hardships
for a chance
to own a place on the honor roll
[Shi Chanli, spring exam candidate]
and climb the ladder of success.
In the following days,
the eyes of the world
will be on the Capital.
All hopes and desperation
will happen here.
We were born to be together.
We are on the same page.
Aren't we fated?
Is this what you think?
Our wedding comes after the spring exam.
Afterward, I will take over
the Imperial Treasury.
The spring exam is the only way
to obstruct me.
Have you come up with a solution?
Yes, indeed.
I'm waiting for Li Chengze's next move.
You ought to be careful.
It doesn't matter if you lose.
At worst,
we resign
and go wandering the world.
As long as you are with me.
Hands off.
You don't want to mess this up.
Speaking of which,
I have been looking at this
since just now.
What is this?
Mandarin ducks playing in the pond.
They are Mandarin ducks?
Well, it's good.
Pretty good.
No need for an excuse.
It's my problem.
When I was learning embroidery,
I liked to do flowers,
leaves, and rocks.
I didn't like living things.
So it's too hard
if I want to learn now.
You don't have to learn that.
Here. Drink some water.
This is for you.
So I must embroider Mandarin ducks.
For me?
This is the wedding custom.
How come there is such a custom?
It's an unwritten rule.
This is what all noble ladies do.
Why didn't you learn this before?
I used to think I couldn't live
long enough to get married.
We are almost there.
We will get married
when the spring exam is over.
By then,
I will embroider
a fine pair of Mandarin ducks.
Why didn't you like embroidering
living things back then?
Even if
I could create vivid embroidery,
they were not living anyway.
It felt like they were trapped here.
When I was little,
I was confined to the palace
and to this sick body
with nowhere to go.
They reminded me
of myself.
It felt uncomfortable.
It's all right now.
I have you.
I grew up in Danzhou.
It's a harbor city.
Many shops come and go every day.
When the sun sets,
the birds fly along with the wind.
The sight is full of lives.
I have never seen one like that before.
To be honest,
I have never left the Capital before.
After we get married,
I will take you there.
I have always had a dream.
When all troubles
can't hold me back anymore,
I will take you to see
all the fine views around the world.
The day will come.
Sir,
do you have a vacant room?
There wasn't any room left
when I came yesterday.
The waiter told me to come this morning
to try my luck.
One moment.
[Shi Chanli, from Shijia Town,
Cangzhou, Hebei Province]
Mr. Shi?
It's me, Shi Chanli.
You are lucky.
A customer just checked out.
There is an empty
quad room.
To be honest,
the spring exam is approaching.
It's not easy to find a room
in the Capital now.
The quad room
may be a little noisy,
but the fee is cheaper.
Are you here for the spring exam?
Yes, of course.
You are a candidate.
May I take a look
at your official document?
I didn't mean anything.
It's because of the strict inspection
as the spring exam is near.
We have to take note of the details.
The authority might come
to inspect later.
Yes, of course.
[Shi Chanli]
Sir.
Do you have a cheaper room?
Even cheaper?
It's fine I don't stay
with other customers.
Don't stay with others?
We don't have rooms like this.
Well, are there services
like you pay for me?
Please don't get me wrong, sir.
I'm saying that I work as a janitor
or an attendant here.
I can work to cover the fee.
Sorry, Mr. Shi.
We have enough workers here.
I will talk about this man.
He ranked way behind me
in the provincial exam.
Unexpectedly, he rose to fame
in the metropolitan exam.
Mr. Shi, are you facing
a financial pinch?
Frankly,
the spring exam is a money pit.
I know there is a solution.
Please tell me, sir.
There is this official
who holds the current spring exam.
If you can meet him,
he might help you.
Who is hosting
the spring exam?
Mr. Fan,
how have you been?
People were amazed
only when they heard
of your poetry fame.
But it's different for me.
When I first set my eyes on you,
I knew your talent
could be peerless.
Who are you?
Mr. Fan.
It's me, He Zongwei.
[He Zongwei, student in the Capital]
We met before.
He...
Oh, He Zongwei. It rings a bell.
You helped Guo Baokun
to sue me in the Capital Magistrate.
Was it you?
Mr. Fan, the Guo family compelled me.
Well, enough. Stop kneeling.
I could only pretend to agree.
In fact, deep inside me,
I despised that.
Get him up.
Enough.
Stand up and talk. Come on.
Thank you, Mr. Wang.
You say you are He Zongwei.
But you look different now.
Faces reflect our thoughts.
Now that I have gotten rid
of the Guo family,
I have become more ambitious
and have a generous-looking face.
Are you saying
that it's the Guo family's fault
and you are clean?
Exactly, Mr. Fan.
I wanted to record
the evildoing of the Guo family
and report it to you one day
to uproot the evil of the country.
But why didn't you report anything?
Well, you acted too quickly.
Guo Youzhi is already in prison,
while I have already
escaped the evil clutch.
It's all
thanks to you, Mr. Fan.
You are like a father to me.
No. You look older than me.
A father who guides my spirit.
Is this a family reunion or something?
I would like to use all my knowledge
to serve the Qing State,
His Majesty,
and you...
Stop right there!
You are a candidate, right?
Yes.
What did you come here for?
Please be my mentor.
You possess shocking talents,
and you rescued my lost soul.
We scholars have deep faith
in great virtues.
If I can't seek an apprenticeship
from you,
this is
simply unconscionable!
So you know I'm the examiner?
Absolutely not, Mr. Fan.
I genuinely admire you, sir.
You know me well.
I strictly carry myself
with dignity and etiquette.
If it wasn't for you,
I wouldn't have brought myself to kneel.
Stand up and talk to me, then.
I will speak on my knees.
I came here with pure sincerity.
Will you
take me as your adopted son?
I'm willing to serve by your side
every day,
Godfather.
First you wanted me to be your mentor,
and now godfather.
Godfather,
I have been struggling
and helpless.
Please grant me my wish, Godfather.
Mr. Fan.
Get up already.
Mr. Fan,
a secret missive
from the First Division.
Do you still remember the Shijia Town?
Of course,
the entire town was wiped out.
There is a survivor now.
[The only survivor of Shijia Town,
Shi Chanli, left the Capital for the exam]
[and arrived yesterday.]
Shi Chanli?
He came to the Capital
for the spring exam
before the Shijia Town was burned,
so he is the only survivor
of the Shijia Town.
He arrived yesterday.
According to the rules,
a student needs to verify his identity
before checking in.
Deng Ziyue got the news
and sent this over immediately.
The only survivor.
The only survivor of the Shijia Town
has come to the Capital.
He stays in an inn here.
Your Highness,
shall I go there?
Why?
Killing a student is easy.
Why do you want to kill him?
Shouldn't we silence him?
I told you
I didn't set the fire in Shijia Town.
Still, he is the survivor.
Fan Xian is still investigating
your past deal with Northern Qi.
All the more reason not to kill him.
The Imperial Inspectorate surely knows
about this by now as you do.
Let him investigate.
I'm also curious about
who set that fire.
♪ The youth raises his head ♪
♪ As he moves toward his moon ♪
♪ People tease him for being delusional ♪
♪ Wondering why he is so unconventional ♪
♪ Wearing a white robe
when crossing a muddy pond ♪
♪ How could it remain unstained? ♪
♪ If silver tael has a value ♪
♪ Who can truly be carefree? ♪
♪ All of you are right ♪
♪ He said: "Please" ♪
♪ "Make way" ♪
♪ "Let me drink until I drop" ♪
♪ On the court ♪
♪ I recite several verses ♪
♪ Let me wear a white robe ♪
♪ And cross the alley
filled with insanity ♪
♪ To scoop up the moon's reflection
in the muddy pond ♪
♪ Sirs, please forgive me ♪
♪ Your words of advice ♪
♪ I understand,
but I don't want to pretend ♪
♪ People search for the golden land ♪
♪ While I search for the moon ♪
♪ Why should we travel together? ♪
♪ Thank you ♪
♪ Excuse me ♪
♪ You are you ♪
♪ I am me ♪
♪ Thank you ♪
♪ Excuse me ♪
♪ You are you ♪
♪ I am me ♪
♪ Wearing a white robe
when crossing a muddy pond ♪
♪ Remarkably worldly-wise
yet hopelessly romantic ♪
♪ Know what you love ♪
♪ Don't change ♪
♪ If one has witnessed
both light and shadow ♪
♪ Yet retains their innocence ♪
♪ They shall be cloaked in moonlight ♪
♪ As they journey through the night ♪